<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Being Human</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Being Human – The Salman Khan Foundation</string>
    <string name="article_text">Being Human – The Salman Khan Foundation is a registered charitable trust established and working in the areas of education and healthcare for the underprivileged.\n
Here is an overview of the projects supported by Being Human Akshara High School, Aseema, Career Development Centers, Educational Resource Center, Maharashtra Prabodhan Seva Mandal (MPSM), Education Support Program for Adivasi Primary Learners, Theatre And Drama Initiative, Being Bajrangi, Tubelight Project. The website of Being Human Foundation is http://www.beinghumanonline.com\n\n
<b>About Salman Khan:</b>
\n\n
<b><i>Early life and ancestry</i></b> - Salman Khan is the eldest son of screenwriter Salim Khan and his first wife Sushila Charak, who adopted the name Salma. Born to a Hindu mother and a Muslim father on 27 December 1965, Khan was brought up in both faiths. In 1980, when Salma and Salim got divorced and his father married the actress Helen, the children\'s relationship with their father grew hostile and only recovered years later.\n\n
<b><i>Career</i></b> — Khan made his acting debut with the 1988 film Biwi Ho To Aisi, which saw him play a supporting role. He went on to play the leading role in Sooraj R. Barjatya\'s romantic family drama Maine Pyar Kiya (1989), which become one of the highest-grossing Indian films at the time. It earned him his first nomination for the Best Actor at Filmfare along with a nomination for Best Male Debut at the same ceremony; the latter was awarded to Barjatya.Maine Pyar Kiya was dubbed in English as When Love Calls, in Spanish as Te Amo, and in Telugu as Prema Paavuraalu.\n\n
<b><i>1994–2009:</i></b> — In 1994, Khan appeared in Rajkumar Santoshi\'s Andaz Apna Apna, co-starring Aamir Khan. At the time of its release, the film failed at the box office but has gained a cult status over the years. Later in the year he collaborated with director Sooraj Barjatya in the romance Hum Aapke Hain Koun..! co-starring Madhuri Dixit. During the 1995 awards season, the film won 3 Filmfare Awards for Best Film, Best Director and Best Actress. It also won the National Award for being the most popular film of the year.\n\n
<b><i>2009–present: Commercial success</i></b> — He appeared in Wanted, directed by choreographer turned director Prabhu Deva. The film received generally positive reviews. Taran Adarsh from Bollywood Hungama rated it 4 of 5 stars noting, WANTED rides on Salman Khan\'s star power. He may not be the best actor in town, but in a film like WANTED, in a role that seems like an extension of his personality, you can\'t think of anyone else enacting this role with flourish.Raja Sen from Rediff gave a rating of 2/5 and said, The writing is both amateurish and crass, while the songs are plain hideous...Khan might be having fun, but the fact a film like Wanted underscores is how badly Bollywood needs a breed of younger leading men. And how the existing lot need roles that fit.\n\n
<b><i>Funding</i></b> — The Organisation designed Little Hearts Programme which was aimed at helping children below poverty line and till sugeries were funded through this programme.The Being Human Foundation programme also have an revenue sharing model understanding with a private company to fund its programmes, and according to this it gets 5.75 percent share from the sale of tees, women\'s wear, kid\'s wear jewellery, flip flops and electric bikes getting sold under Being Human brand.\n\n
</string>
    <string name="add_comment">ADD COMMENT</string>
</resources>